# **SULE SOLACE ADAMU**

sulesolace.adamu@gmail.com | +234-814-545-1108

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Front end developer dedicated to helping clients accomplish technical goals by developing user friendly and forward-thinking websites and web-based apps. Experience working across the full-stack of web development. Quality-focused developer with a history of working well in fast-paced, challenging, and team-oriented environments.

#### EDUCATION -

Bachelor of Engineering (B.Eng.), Computer Engineering
University of Maiduguri, Borno State, Nigeria.

Expected Graduation: May 2023

- Current Cumulative GPA: 3.89/5.00
- Relevant Coursework: Computer Programming, Data Structure and Algorithm, Computer Networking, Computer Architecture, Embedded System

#### WORK EXPERIENCE-

# **Computer Engineering Intern**

**January 2022 – July 2022** 

ICT Center, Nigerian Army University, Biu.

Borno State, Nigeria.

- Built a user-friendly website which is compatible across multiple browsers for the school e-Library.
- Used React.js to develop a system to digitize the documentation of employee training
- Assisted a small team of students with building multiple internal applications using HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Analyzed network protocols and maintenance of the entire network structures of the institution.

## Freelance Web Developer

**May 2020 – December 2021** 

Fiverr.com, Freelancer.com, Upwork.com

Remote

- Built user friendly landing pages for clients using simple and reusable codes.
- Built beautiful user interfaces for clients without compromising functionality for aesthetics.
- Implemented newly-learned front-end object-oriented programming to develop client server systems.
- Tested React components using Jest.

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS -

- Computing: Microsoft Office Suite, WIX, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL.
- Professional: Problem Solving, Critical Thinking, Technical Writing, Leadership